questions_python = [
    {
     "question": "What will the following expression return: type(None)?",
        "choices": ["1. 'NoneType'", "2. 'int'", "3. 'str'", "4. 'object'", "5. 'boolean'"],
        "correct_answer": ["NoneType", "1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Python data type?",
        "choices": ["1. String", "2. Boolean", "3. Undefined", "4. Float", "5. Null"],
        "correct_answer": ["undefined", "3"]  # Only 'undefined' is not a valid Python data type
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to declare a constant in Python?",
        "choices": ["1. var", "2. let", "3. const", "4. constant", "5. None"],
        "correct_answer": ["None", "5"]  # Python doesn't have a specific keyword for constants
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a falsy value in Python?",
        "choices": ["1. 0", "2. 'false'", "3. []", "4. 'true'", "5. {}"],
        "correct_answer": ["0", "1"]  # '0' is falsy in Python
    },
    {
        "question": "What will the following expression return: type(None)?",
        "choices": ["1. 'NoneType'", "2. 'int'", "3. 'str'", "4. 'object'", "5. 'boolean'"],
        "correct_answer": ["NoneType", "1"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the correct syntax for creating a function in Python?",
        "choices": ["1. def myFunction[] {}", "2. def = myFunction() {}", "3. function myFunction() {}", "4. def myFunction():", "5. myFunction() function {}"],
        "correct_answer": ["def myFunction():", "4"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following methods can be used to join two lists in Python?",
        "choices": ["1. join()", "2. concat()", "3. merge()", "4. combine()", "5. extend()"],
        "correct_answer": ["extend", "5"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the output of the following code: print(2 + '2')?",
        "choices": ["1. 22", "2. 4", "3. '22'", "4. TypeError", "5. 2"],
        "correct_answer": ["TypeError", "4"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is used to stop a loop in Python?",
        "choices": ["1. exit", "2. stop", "3. break", "4. continue", "5. return"],
        "correct_answer": ["break", "3"]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the default value of a variable declared with 'None' in Python, if not initialized?",
        "choices": ["1. 0", "2. None", "3. null", "4. NaN", "5. False"],
        "correct_answer": ["None", "2"]
    }
]
